In this clip, were just going to talk about the elements of the track.
The key element of this track is that it is a dirt track, and not a pavement track.
So they constantly are watering the track to keep, to try to keep the track in race condition.
The inside of the track, where the berm is, it's not really built up right now, but there is a berm up there.
You want to stay between the boundaries of the berm and the wall.
The wall protects the fans, the drivers; the catch bench is the very important part of the track.
You know, if you start flipping and you don't want to go into the stands, because you can injure people in the stands it also keeps you inside the track, so you are not going to injury yourself by flipping over and hitting something outside the track.
The flagman stands in that stand right over there.
And this is corner one, two, three and four.
Coming out of corner four, that's where the start line is for the re-start and the original start.
Where the flag stand is, about, you know, give or take ten feet of this flag stand, or back from this flag stand on every track is the start finish line.
We have lights in all four corners and in the middle of the track so that you can know when yellow flag are, know when there is red flag if somebody is injured and know you know if its green, white flag.
Those are very big safety things.